Introducing English Pod, this Justine, featuring, don't spoil it, featuring La Diva del Barrio,
the highest pitched voice in the podcastosphere.
Here with us directly from Spanishpod.com Liliana Zmata.
Hey! You almost forgot my last name.
Hello, La Diva!
Hello everyone, welcome to English Pod.
As Marco said, we're here joined with Liliana Mata, who is the host of Spanish Pod.
The host of Spanish Pod!
So after a very long awaited time, we finally have her here in the studio.
Bravo, bravo Liliana, granda plazo.
Yeah, but I want to say that I was kind of angry at you guys.
Now why? Why are you here now?
Because I was the second one.
What? What?
No, no, no.
Who's doing that?
I'm not, I'm not.
No, it's that we wanted to dedicate an entire show only for you.
Thank you.
We didn't want you to share the microphone with another girl.
That's really nice.
That's why.
It's so true.
Yes.
So why are we here for her?
Hey, and you're back.
Yes, you're back, Leo.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Big round of applause, bro.
Leo, where have you been? What happened?
So how was your trip?
It was amazing.
Do you know that in Japan, you have like these vendor machines
where you put a few dollars in and you get an iPad?
No way.
Not a few dollars.
That's not true.
I told you that today.
Also, can you make it with all coins of one, like $1.50
to get to the price of an iPad?
So, but OK, first of all, I think that we haven't introduced Liliana well enough.
We did like, as you said, we want to give like the appropriate honors.
Yeah, the appropriate honors.
Thank you. Thank you for your English.
And so we should listen to Liliana's profile right now.
Liliana Mata came to be known by the world as a child dancing star
from the early age of three.
She was dancing her way into the hearts of millions.
And by the age of 11, she was a backup dancer for Madonna.
Unfortunately, her premature launch into fame
resulted in having many negative influences.
She constantly partied with her best friends, Brittany Spears and Paris Hilton,
which caused her career to end.
After months in rehab, she stumbled upon the podcasting world
and with her charisma and ample knowledge of Spanish, became the host
of what the world considers to be the best Spanish teaching resource online.
Spanish part. Wow.
We did. Yeah, interesting.
I did not know about that.
That thing. That was that was good.
The part in Casablanca was actually a bit astonishing.
It's Google. You can find out anything about anyone on Google.
So you've been working with her all this time.
The power of the internet.
Yes. Interesting.
All right. So I hope you enjoyed Liliana's profile.
And well, she's going to help us out today
introducing this week's lessons and also other news.
Introducing this week's lesson.
I just touched Liliana's leg, by the way.
OK, that is inappropriate.
You're fired. You're fired.
I'm on fire.
You're always on fire. I see.
Thank you, Liliana.
OK, for Monday, we have a lesson on the Formula One racing.
You went to the Formula One.
Yeah, Shanghai Circuit, the Formula One.
It was really cool, but it actually rained, so it wasn't that nice.
But it gets a little bit more challenging for the drivers.
Yeah, the drivers were spinning and flying off the track.
So that was cool. Yeah, it was nice.
So who won?
This German guy named...
Did you really care, Liliana?
Yes. Come on.
Do you even know?
OK, name three drivers that are driving Formula One.
Easy, easy.
Alonso, Schumacher, OK, when he wasn't retired.
When he wasn't retired.
No, too bad, too bad.
This is so unfair.
It's like if I ask you something girly, you're not going to know.
Come on, come on, let's take that challenge.
One each, OK? I'm ready.
And I think I'll challenge you.
I think I can I can give you the answer in 10 seconds.
Whatever the question is.
Really? Yes. Whatever question.
Let me take out my iPhone.
OK, give me three types of makeups.
Powder.
Thirteen and one.
See, see, he knows.
I told you, you mean brands, brands are more specific.
Yes, brands, three brands.
I OK. One, two, three.
Lancome, Lancome or whatever that's spelled.
OK, but your time is up.
No, you have just one.
OK, one, two, three, four, five.
Your time is up.
And the full La Paris.
And Séfora.
Séfora.
No, that's that's the whole store.
It's not a brand.
Well, whatever I want. I want.
Yeah, I know you want.
Oh, my God.
It's already done.
Is this Macho Pod or something?
No, like we're so frustrated in the real life
because we cannot get any girl or anything.
We come here and we feel better about ourselves.
Yeah, I can tell.
Yeah, shut up.
So annoying.
All right.
And on Wednesday, we're going to have an educational lesson.
International Workers Day, May 1st.
May 1st.
OK, we get to work that day.
Yeah, we have to work.
So but not in every country with the celebrations.
Yeah, in the US, oddly enough, it's not celebrated
because they don't care about the workers.
I don't know.
But actually, international workers, they started.
The whole movement started in the US.
So it's weird.
Why don't they give the just moved the day up?
I don't know.
The movement moved away from the US.
And they're just like, oh, right.
Yeah, you don't need us.
We don't need you.
We're taking our holiday somewhere else.
We do celebrate in Mexico, right?
Yes.
May 1st.
3 Mera ama yu.
So you have a holiday on that day.
Yes, you don't work, yeah.
Now, the interesting thing is in some countries,
companies will do something for the workers on that day,
like a trip or a party.
We have a concert in Rome usually
for the first May holiday in Italy.
You have a what?
There's always a big concert in Rome organized
by the city every 1st of May.
So they don't work.
You don't work.
No, you never worked, right?
Well, the people who work for the concert,
they have to work, right?
Yeah, I don't know how that works.
Maybe they worked the day before.
And they knew everything there.
Everything's ready.
All right.
And on Friday, we have an interesting lesson
because we have some sci-fi aficionados out there.
So we have Funky Galaxy Battles,
which is very similar, oddly enough, to Star Wars.
Not to battle Star Galactica.
Funky what?
No, no, no.
Galaxy Battles.
But what is this?
Is this the name of the dialogue?
Three names now.
Funky.
Galaxy.
Battle.
Yeah, but is this a program?
No, it's going to be a podcast.
We might make it into a series.
Look at me.
Funky.
It's a series.
So I know Liliana is a very big Battle Star Galactica fan.
Yes.
No way.
Such a geek.
I'm not a geek.
Seriously, you know what it is, basically?
It's like a soap opera like Cataleno Vela in space.
How cool is that?
It's a bit like Star Wars.
Exactly, it's a geek.
No, you're a geek.
That's a cool, cool idea.
That's a geek answer.
No, it's not.
But it's over, right?
It finished?
Well, I don't know.
I'm still watching it.
And I watched the whole thing.
So now we're going to reveal the ending to Liliana.
No, no, no.
So you can watch the podcast now and come back.
At the end, she dies.
No.
What other shows do you watch?
And then The Kiss.
Sci-fi?
Yeah.
No, that's it.
Or any other show that you enjoy?
Mm, there's a bunch.
You're a big show fan, or what's it called?
A series.
TV series.
Yeah, I love TV.
Yeah, definitely.
I love it.
I like Dexter.
OK, now it's the moment for Liliana's top three of TV
series in the history of the world.
Yeah, in the history.
In the history.
Wow, ever, ever in the world.
Favourite of all time.
OK, that's going to be difficult.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Friends.
I love friends.
Friends, number three.
Friends is a classic, yeah.
Number three.
That's one.
Number two.
There, Dexter.
Number one.
I know.
I'm not with you on that.
No, it's really good.
It's OK.
It's OK, but not number two.
A lot of people didn't like Friends.
They said it was too unreal, that it was.
I love Friends.
I thought it was OK.
Yeah, it was all right.
Seinfeld for me.
Seinfeld, Seinfeld.
Seinfeld is a good one.
California-cation, man.
I say this and that in this part.
OK, enough.
Number one.
Sex and the City.
What?
Oh, gosh.
Spicy, spicy.
It's a classic.
Spicy.
Spicy opinion.
No, imagine, this, when it started,
it was taboo to talk about sex that much, you know?
But how can women like that show?
And it just shows this, like, very superficial.
Because girls are superficial.
No, no, no, no, no.
But there's episodes.
She didn't hear.
There's episodes.
No, it's true.
I agree.
There's some episodes that are so, like, superficial and
stupid and very general.
But there's some that they speak about a lot of
situations of different women.
Love, love.
So universal themes that you can relate, everybody can
relate to.
Maybe that's the key.
I don't think guys watch that one.
Oh, and he loves it.
You like the sex and the city?
Leo has watched it with me, and he laughs.
And let me tell you, you have to learn a lot of things
about women watching that video.
That is true.
He's trying to spin the whole thing in a macho way.
But it's OK.
We know you're a sensitive guy.
I use it to pick up girls.
Well, I love it.
No, but it's true.
He's right.
So you and Lily are sitting there on the couch with a
bucket of ice cream, tissues.
All right, so those are our three lessons
coming out next week.
Not here, Liliana.
Hey, shut up.
Stop it.
Marco, say something.
No, seriously, Liliana, you have to stop.
You're fired, Liliana.
You're fired.
Harassment.
Sexual harassment in the office.
Are you going to be back next week?
No.
Why?
Do you want to say anything to the users of EnglishPod?
Yes.
They love you.
Do you want to say a goodbye message or something?
And you know, there's actually a user who, well,
there are a couple of users from Mexico as well.
Oh, really?
There's a girl from Monterey, if you want to say hi.
Hey, Cuevas.
Grande Cuevas.
I think she's backing up the girls on the podcast.
Cuevas, thank you so much for supporting the girls.
She wants you guys to come back, so hopefully you won't let her down.
Yeah, I won't.
All right.
I'll fight for our rights.
Yeah.
All right, so a big shout out to all the girls out there.
I hope you're not mad.
We love everyone.
We love especially them, actually.
Yeah, yeah.
Hell, yeah.
Not in that sense, a little.
Oh, oh.
All right, guys, so we'll see you guys next time.
Take care.
Ciao.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
EnglishPod.com.